ponystars.com 2009-03-09

# Acclaim Message Boards :: View topic - Privacy Policy

ACCLAIM Staff  

Site Admin  

| Joined: 13 Apr 2006  
---  
Posts: 641  
| 

Privacy Policy

We take the privacy of our customers very seriously and as you will read, you are protected by our commitment to the following: 

1\. We will never sell or transfer your personal information to any other third party company.   
2\. We collect the following information: 

\- User ID : To identify yourself and access your account   
\- Password : To protect your account   
\- ZIP Code : We provide the Zip Code to our advertising partners.   
\- Country : Some of our games are not available in countries where other publishers own the distribution rights. We use the - Country to allow access to our games. We provide the Country to our advertising partners.   
\- Gender: We provide the Gender to our advertising partners.   
\- Birthday : To validate the age to comply with COPA rules and we provide the birthday to our advertising partners.   
\- Valid Email address : We collect the email only for if you are 13 or older or we have received the permssion of the Parent or Legal Guardian. You can use the email to retrieve your User ID if you have forgotten it. Based on your email selections, we will email you information about our games such as updates and new games. You will never receive emails from us with offerings on behalf of other companies.   
\- Character name : Used in the DANCE! game to name the player's character.   
\- IP Address : Each and every time you log on your IP address will be collected in order to protect you in case someone other than you is using your account. We provide the IP Address to our advertising partners.   
\- Cookies : We store cookies on your PC to keep track of your Account and it is not shared with other companies.

3\. When a child under 13 years of age signs up we not collect the Email address without the permission of the Parent or Legal Guardian and we will collect the other items listed above. We do not collect anything else. If a child under 13 years of age wants to post information on our website or chat with other players, we will require that they do not disclose any personal information such as the real name, address, phone number and anything that can be used to contact the child.   
4\. Once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left our Website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. 

This game incorporates technology of Massive Incorporated and IGA Incorporated that enables certain in-game objects   
(e.g. advertising) to be temporarily uploaded to your PC and replaced in-game while connected online. As part of that process, no personally identifiable information about you is collected and only select non-personally identifiable information is temporarily logged. No logged information is used to determine any personally identifiable information about you. For full details see <http://www.massiveincorporated.com/privacy.htm> and <http://www.ingameadvertising.com/>

When purchasing game items or subscriptions to our games, you will have the choice to pay by Paypal, Click&Buy, mobile phone, bill to your home phone or any other e-commerce available today or in the future. We will collect the required information for each payment method, however, this information will be kept confidential and is only shared under industry standard security methodologies to the billing partners. The billing partners have no right to use your information other than completing the billing process you have initiated. 

We ask that you educate your child to never give out email, name, address, phone or pager information without parents consent. Tell them to always notify a parent OR guardian, when they feel threatened, or are asked for any personal information. The Parent needs to contact us immediately. 

For complaints or to remove your Child's information, we can be reached via e-mail at 

You can send us mail at: 

Acclaim Games Incorporated   
9595 Wilshire Blvd. Suite 900   
Beverly Hills , CA 90212   
United States of America   
Phone: (310) 492-5188   
Fax: (310) 943-2332 

For visitors to our website, we look at the IP address to decide if we can grant access. We may deny access to identified violators of our terms of use, those who violated our privacy policies and those from countries we do not have rights to publish some of our games. We keep every IP address in a log file that is also used for mark eting research and is also provided to our advertisement partners. 

If we materially change our privacy policy, we will notify you when you sign on or send you an email if we have collected it. We will offer you the choice to agree to it or to delete your account should you refuse to agree to the new privacy policy. 

You can change your information with the exception of the User ID anytime by visiting [www.acclaim.com,](http://www.acclaim.com%2C/) signing on and then choosing the My Account link on the upper right side of the website. 

In the event that we sell a portion or our entire Company, we will include provisions in the selling contract requiring the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same manner required by this Privacy Policy. 

We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or will help to enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of our Web sites.
